早上好
Good morning.
一小时前  我辞去了库克县州检察官职务
An hour ago, I resigned as state's attorney of Cook County.
我心情沉重
I did this with a heavy heart
将与那些诽谤性指控抗争到底
And a deep commitment to fight these scurrilous charges.
我要强调
I want to be clear.
我从未滥用职权
I have never abused my office.
我从未因钱色贿赂
I have never traded lighter sentences for financial
而给人减刑
Or sexual favors.
但是  我愧对妻子艾丽西娅和两个孩子
At the same time, I need to atone for my personal failings
我要向他们赎罪
With my wife, Alicia, and our two children.
那些交易所涉款项  是我个人财产
The money used in these transactions was mine...
全都是
And mine alone.
我从未动用公款
No public funds were ever utilized.
但我承认
But I do admit to a failure of
我与那些女人确实存在不正当关系
judgment in my privity with these women.
我和艾丽西娅
Alicia and I...
请求媒体尊重我们的隐私
Ask that the press please respect our privacy.
给我们时间平复伤痛
Give us time to heal.
有上帝的保佑和家人的宽恕
With the love of god, and the forgiveness of my family,
我相信能赢回他们的信任
I know I can rebuild their trust.
我要感谢芝加哥民众
I want to thank the people of Chicago.
很荣幸为你们服务
It has been an honor to serve you.
我希望有朝一日
And I pray that one day,
能再次为你们服务  谢谢
I may serve you again. Thank you.
请问你和妓女还保持着关系吗
Sir! Are you still involved with prostitutes, sir?
你与多少女人有染
How many were there, sir?
你还会再担任公职吗
Will you ever try to hold public office again?
请回答
Sir! Answer the question!
已经安排了《论坛报》和第四频道的采访
We have interviews set up with the Tribune and Channel Four.
我绝对不再接受任何采访
Absolutely not. I'm not doing any more interviews.
全都给我取消
I want you to cancel all of them. That's it.
我会告诉第二频道
I'll tell Channel Two
我们现在无可奉告
We don't have a comment at the present time.
但就此事的真实性深表怀疑
But we emphatically question the authenticity of this thing.
你没事吧
You all right?
福瑞克夫人
Mrs. Florrick, how long have you known
你何时知道丈夫有外遇的
Your husband was having an affair?
你打算怎么保护你的孩子
How are you going to protect your children?
请问  不是9点半开会吗
Excuse me, isn't the staff meeting at 9:30?
不是这间会议室  在楼上呢
You're in the wrong conference room. It's up one floor.
天啊
God...
这是一项大型集团诉讼
This is a major class action.
能帮我们奠定顶级律所的地位
A case that could propel us to the top rank of full service firms,
这对年终奖金的影响
And I don't think I need to remind you
不用我多说了吧
What that will do to your year-end bonuses.
不过  谢弗林公司解聘了上一家律所
Anyway, Sheffrin-Marks fired their last firm
是因为他们不够专心
Because they took their eye off the ball.
所以  除非另行通知
So, until further notice,
你们的私生活全都取消了
Your personal lives have been cancelled.
你们有些人
So, we'll need some of you
要去帮着处理小客户案件
To help out with the lower profile client work
让我们的顶级律师腾出手来
To free up our top litigators.
艾迪  公路再分配案你去准备证词
Ed, you take the witness prep on highway redistribution.
东  布赖顿的犯人交给你了
Don, you take the Brighton criminal.
艾丽西娅负责那个法律援助案
And Alicia will take the pro bono.
其余人等
Everyone else,
你们要给谢弗林公司展现我们最强大的能力
your task is to show sheffrin-marks our "A" game, okay?
干活儿吧
Let's do this.
威尔
Will.
艾丽西娅
Alicia.
抱歉没跟大家介绍一下你
I'm sorry I didn't introduce you in there.
这项集团诉讼忙坏我们了
Everything's moving real fast with this class action.
我是要感谢你给我这个机会
Well, I just wanted to say thank you for the opportunity.
简直救我一命
It's a real life saver.
哪里  很高兴你能来
No, glad you could come aboard.
希望你能办好这个法律援助案
Hope you're all right with this pro bono.
感觉怎么样
How'd it sound?
-很有意思  -很好
- Interesting.  - Good.
别紧张  你对枪弹残留没把握吗
Don't be nervous. You worried about the gunshot residue?
那个...  天啊
The, um... Oh, god.
铃声不错嘛  谁设的
Nice ring tone. Who gets that?
是我婆婆  我女儿编写的
Oh, my mother-in-law. My daughter programmed it.
你的呢
And what's yours?
别提啦
I don't want to know.
关于枪弹残留...
So, um, the gun residue...
戴安  你给艾丽西娅介绍下情况吧
Diane, you're briefing Alicia, right?
很好  她来我就放心了
Good. You're in good hands.
抓紧做  然后吃晚饭
So, let's catch up, have dinner.
威尔对你评价很高
So, Will speaks highly of you.
他说你从乔治城大学毕业时  是班里第一名
He says you graduated top of your class at Georgetown.
啥时候毕业的
When was this?
-15年前  -哦
-15 years ago. - Uh-huh.
然后你在哪儿干了2年来着
And you spent two years at...
高诗雅  埃布拉姆斯 & 阿博特律所
Crozier, Abrams & Abbott.
这律所不错
Good firm.
威尔说  你在那儿完成的计费工时是最多的
Will says you clocked the highest billable hours there.
后来为啥不干了
Why did you leave?
因为孩子  还有彼得的工作
Well, the kids and Peter's career.
布莱恩  把卷宗给福瑞克女士
Brian! Can you get Mrs. Florrick the files?
好的
Mm-hmm. Sure.
你就把我当作导师吧  艾丽西娅
I want you to think of me as a mentor, Alicia.
这和镇上的校友关系
It's the closest thing we have
是最相似的
To an old boys' network in this town.
女人帮助女人  可以吗
Women helping women, okay?
好的
Okay.
我出道时  听过一条很棒的建议
When I was starting out, I got one great piece of advice.
男人可以懒惰  女人不行
Men can be lazy. Women can't.
这句话对你加倍适用
And I think that goes double for you.
不仅是因为
Not only are you
你重返工作岗位太晚
Coming back to the workplace fairly late,
而且你还有很不好的名声
But you have some very prominent baggage.
但既然她能扛住  你也能
But, hey, if she can do it, so can you.
多谢  布莱恩
Thanks, Brian.
和很多律所一样  我们工时的5%
Like many law firms, we donate five percent
献给法律援助案
Of billable hours to pro bono.
很遗憾  这案子早就超过我的工时量了
Sadly, I'm long past my quote on this one.
詹妮弗·刘易斯  26岁
Jennifer Lewis. 26 years old.
教二年级
Taught second grade.
被控谋杀其前夫
Accused of killing her ex-husband.
起诉方以为能让她稳坐45年牢
Prosecution thought it was a slam dunk 45 years,
但是陪审团上周却陷入僵局
But the jury came back last week deadlocked.
六个陪审员投票她有罪  六个投没有
Six jurors voted to convict, six not.
我甚至不明白为什么州检察官
I'm not even sure why the state attorney
要再次审判  除非他想要...维持正义
Is re-trying except he wants... justice!
他想证明自己  所以你要延用
He wants to prove himself. So, stick with my strategy
我第一次审讯时的策略  警察在调查中
From the first trial. The police focused
过早地锁定了詹妮弗
On Jennifer so early in the investigation,
而根本没找过那个劫车人
They never even looked for the carjacker.
所以  让陪审团再次陷入僵局
Deadlock a jury a second time,
他们不可能再陷入僵局了  明白吗
They'll never re-try a third. Okay?
好  我们的调查员会帮你赶上
Okay, our investigator can get you up to speed
3点的保释听证会
For the bail hearing at 3:00.
科马克  我准备好了
Cormac, I'm ready.
听证会是今天吗
The hearing's today?
也可以推迟  但是那样
Well, we could delay, but that would leave
詹妮弗就得再监禁一个月
Jennifer incarcerated for another month.
别担心  没事的
Don't worry. You'll be fine.
美国教育机构不会反对保释的
The ASA's not going to argue against a recognizance release.
走  10点半开会
Let's go. Meeting's at 10:30.
但我承认私下里同这些女人打交道时
But I do admit to a failure of judgment
没有把持住
In my private dealings with these women...
对不起
Sorry.
...是我个人财产  全都是
...Mine and mine alone.
从没未动用公款
No public funds were ever utilized.
最新消息...
The recent news...
我来帮你
Oh, hey. Let me help you with that.
不用  我可以
No, I'm fine.
没事  反正我也要去那边
No, no, I'm heading that way anyway.
我是凯里  另一个新来的副手
I'm Cary, the other new associate.
我记得你  我是艾丽西娅
Oh, right. Alicia.
我知道我们俩会是竞争对手
Yeah, look, I know we should be at each other's throats,
但是我只是想说
But I just want to say I really
我真的很敬佩你的能力
Respect what you doing here,
既能照顾家里  又能投身到工作中
Raising a family and then jumping right back into this.
我妈妈  她也想像你这样
My mom, she's thinking of doing the same thing.
-很好  -是啊
- Great. - Yeah.
你跟了法律援助案吧
So, you're on the pro bono, right?
太棒了
Yeah, that's great.
去年暑假我还参加了无罪计划的实习
I interned last summer at the innocence project.
我爸最好的朋友是巴瑞·谢克
My dad's best friend is Barry Scheck
感觉太棒了
And it was just amazing.
帮助别人  所以他们让我来谢弗林公司上班
Helping people. Here, they got me on the sheffrin-marks.
这肯定很有挑战性
I'm sure it will be challenging,
但是一天过去了  你都做了些什么
But at the end of the day, what have you really done?
为公司节省了几百亿吗
Saved a corporation a few billion dollars?
你想交换吗
You want to trade?
我也想啊  但是貌似他们另有安排
I would, but I guess they have other plans, so...
凯里  我差不多了  拿铁在你桌上
I am almost done, Cary. The latte's on your desk.
-谢谢  -你好  福瑞克夫人
-Thank you.- Hi, Mrs. Florrick.
貌似我们共用一个助手
Looks like we share an assistant,
如果我霸占她了就跟我说  好吗
So tell me when I'm hogging her, okay?
胜利属于强者
And let the best man win.
你说什么
Excuse me?
胜利...
Uh, let the...
没什么
Nothing.
没什么  我...
It's nothing. I...
没什么
It's nothing.
不好意思
Oops.
没紧张  是你办公室
Don't worry, it's yours.
我是凯琳达·夏尔马  自己人
Kalinda Sharma. I'm the in-house.
就是那个调查员
Oh, the investigator.
你是彼得·福瑞克的夫人
You're peter Florrick's wife.
是的
That's right.
我在州检察官办公室干了3年
I worked with him at the state's attorney's office three years
却被他开除了
He fired me.
好吧
Okay
你都知道些什么
So, what do you know?
客户是个二年级老师
The client is a second- grade school teacher.
-詹妮弗...  -刘易斯
- Jennifer...- Lewis.
因谋杀她前夫被捕
She was arrested for killing her ex-husband.
掩饰成了汽车劫案
Making it look like a botched carjacking.
发现在詹妮弗的
Gunshot residue
脸上还有手上有枪弹残留
Was found on Jennifer's face and hands.
于是警察认定那是
That's why the cops started to think it was a murder
掩饰成劫车案的谋杀
Disguised as a carjacking.
他们认为  詹妮弗枪杀了她前夫
According to them, Jennifer shot her ex-husband
-然后把枪擦了干净  -动机呢
- And wiped down the gun. - And the motive?
他已经再婚  并且想争夺三岁孩子的监护权
He remarried and wanted custody of the three-year-old.
目击者称  案发前一周见过他们争吵
Witnesses saw them arguing a week before the murder.
妈咪  快接电话
Hey, mom. Pick up the phone.
hey, mom. Pick up the phone.
-妈咪  快...  -不好意思  是我女儿
- Hey, mom. Pick up... - Sorry, that's my daughter.
喂  格雷斯
Hi, Grace.
妈妈  我想问你个问题
Hey, mom. I want to ask you a question,
但是别惊慌  好吗
But I don't want you to freak out, okay?
算了  我还是问扎克吧
Forget it. I'll ask Zach.
-别别  什么事  -好吧
- No, no, no. what? - All right, well,
有女生说我爸和妙龄妓女上床  我...
Some girl said dad slept with a hooker my age. and I just...
-什么  -女士  请把手机关掉
- What? - Ma'am, you'll have to turn that off.
他们还在电脑室放录像
They were playing the tape in the computer lab.
那女生还说
And some girl said
她爸是警察  他说其中一个妓女
Her dad's a cop and he said one of the hookers
还不满20岁
Was a teenager.
首先  她们都满了20岁了
Okay, first of all, they were all over 20 and second,
其次  老师在哪
Where's the teacher?
没什么  妈  我去写作业了
It's no big deal, mom. look, I've got homework.
晚点再跟你说
I'll talk to you later.
怎么了
What?
我上一次进法庭是13年前的事了
Last time I was in court was 13 years ago.
那时我才12岁
Wow. I was 12.
谢谢夸奖
Thanks.
法官把手伸到他袋里
The judge reaches into his pocket,
拿出一张支票  递给原告
Pulls out a check, handing it to the plaintiff.
"我还回你5000美元  稍后"
"I'm returning five grand and we're going to decide this."
那是福瑞克的妻子
That's Florrick's wife.
艾丽西娅  我的天
Alicia? My god.
马坦  记得吗  在部门的圣诞晚会上
Matan, remember? From the department christmas party.
你现在在斯特恩  洛克哈特&加德纳律所做事吗
You're at Stern, Lockhart & Gardner?
是啊  第一天上班
Yeah. First day.
这位是桑德拉·佩  是新手
This is Sandra Pai. She's new.
彼得离开后加入的
Since Peter...
顺便问下  他最近怎样
How's he doing, by the way?
彼得吗  他很好
Peter? Fine.
替我问候他  好吗
Say hello for me, will you?
看看这些
Look at all this.
你打算击败我们了
You're going to bury us.
我不知道你怎么办到的  艾丽西娅
I don't know how you do it, Alicia.
换成我  早缩在角落里不出来丢人了
I'd be huddled up in a ball somewhere.
工作吧
Well, back to work.
祝你好运
Good luck.
戴安呢
Where's Diane?
戴安叫全权负责这起案件
Diane asked me to step in for her.
詹妮弗  我是艾丽西娅·福瑞克
Jennifer, I'm Alicia Florrick.
是律所的另一位律师
I'm one of the other lawyers with the firm.
插手吗  多久啊
Step in? For how long?
整个重审阶段
For the retrial.
天哪
My god
全体起立
All rise.
女士
Ma'am.
库克县刑事法庭
The criminal court
现在开庭
Of Cook County is now in session,
由尊敬的法官理查德·奎斯特主持庭审
The honorable judge Richard Cuesta presiding.
请坐
Be seated.
好吧  让我们先来听下双方陈述
Okay, let's hear it.
尊敬的法官大人  我刚刚
Your honor, I just...
尊敬的法官大人  请您回顾一下
Your honor, just to refresh your memory,
被告被视为畏罪潜逃
The accused was deemed a flight risk
因为她在先前的监护权听证会上
Due to an earlier custody hearing
企图携其女儿潜逃
In which she threatened to run off with her daughter.
可是上周陪审团就这起谋杀案投票
And yet just last week a jury deadlocked
结果是六票对六票的僵局  布罗迪先生
On these murder charges six to six, Mr.Brody.
我知道我们的新州检察官
Now I know our new state's attorney
想看上去强硬些  但是为何要重审此案呢
Wants to look tough, but why are you fighting this?
法官大人  我只想...
Your honor, I just wanted to...
大家都准备好
The people are prepared to
开始重审了  法官大人
Retry this case right now, your honor.
如果福瑞克女士
If Mrs. Florrick
坚持要替委托人洗脱罪名
Is so intent on getting her client out,
为何她不赞成快速审判呢
Why doesn't she agree to a speedy trial?
-福瑞克女士  -是的  法官大人
- Mrs.Florrick? - Yes, your honor.
受人尊敬的彼得·福瑞克的妻子
The wife of the esteemed Peter Florrick?
你丈夫和我向来
Your husband and I never quite
意见相悖  女士
Saw eye to eye, ma'am
法官大人
Your honor
福瑞克女士  听我说
Mrs. Florrick, don't talk.
倘若原告认为这在某些方面
But if the prosecution thinks that this will in some way
会使我对你的委托人存有偏见的话
Prejudice me against your client,
他就大错特错了
He is sorely mistaken.
省点力吧  马坦
Nice try, Matan.
所以刘易斯女士理所应当
So Ms.Lewis is granted
审前释放
Pretrial release
通过电子追踪器
With electronic monitoring.
她的行动会被受限于临时住所
She is restricted to temporary housing,
以及代理人办公室之间
Attorney's offices, and transit in between.
鉴于这是重审
And given that this is a rerun,
我把再审日期定在25号
I'll set the trial date for the 25th.
现在  都满意了吧  很好
Now, are we all happy? Good.
谢谢你
Thank you.
没什么
Sure.
我们曾处得很好
We had a nice time
迈克尔说他想女儿
Michael talked about missing his daughter,
想我们在一起的时光
The life we had together.
我们正开车回家
We were driving home
接着
And, uh...
爆胎了
...we got a flat.
他出去修理
He was getting out to fix it,
然后我看到
And i saw...
一辆红色敞篷卡车
A red pickup truck.
有个人走近了迈克尔
A man came up to Michael.
本来我没看见枪
I didn't see the gun
直到
Until...
迈克尔
Michael!
我看到迈克尔的脸
And I saw Michael's face.
已经...
It was, um...
要不要休息一下
Do you need to take a break?
不用了
Uh, no.
可以的话给我瓶水
Just-- if there was some water.
当然
Sure.
索尼娅  拿瓶水
Sonia, we need some water in here.
5分钟后送来
It's going to be about five minutes,
我还得上楼帮他做份同行比对
But then I've got to do his depo upstairs.
好吧  你做好了告诉我
Okay, uh, tell me when you're done.
你说这人从这里跑到红色卡车那儿
You say this man ran to a red pickup truck here,
接着从这方向穿过停车场离开
And took off in this direction across the parking lot.
这里有监视器
There's a surveillance camera here.
原告播放了录像  证明你在说谎
And the prosecution played it to make you look like a liar.
我没说谎
I'm not lying.
但是带子上根本没有卡车
But there's no truck on the tape.
这就是为何你正面临
And that's why you're facing a
重审而不是无罪释放
Retrial now and not an acquittal
我认为凯琳达想说的是  詹妮弗
I think what Kalinda is trying to say, Jennifer...
是否有可能是你自己搞错了
...is, is it possible that you were mistaken
那车开了这条路  而不是那条
And that the car went this way-- not that way?
你女儿吗
Is that your daughter?
他们不准我看她
They won't let me see her.
监护权在迈克尔父母手里
Michael's parents have custody.
我该怎么办
What am I going to do?
总有一天你会拿回监护权的
You're going to take it one day at a time.
我们给你安排了住所
We got you housing.
你先去那里
You're going to go there,
洗个澡  好好睡一觉
Take a shower, take a nap.
不要看电视
Don't turn on the tv.
喜欢看书吗
You like reading?
我会拿点书给你
I'm going to get you some books.
小说最合适
Fiction is best.
你可能不想  但还是要好好打扮下
You won't feel like it, but put on nice clothes and makeup.
勉强一下
Force yourself to.
不是为了上庭
Not for court--
为了自己
For you.
现在表面工作才最关键
It's the superficial things that matter most right now.
这能让案子有点起色吗
Does it ever get easier?
不会
No.
但你会感觉好点
But you do get better at it.
怎么了
What?
如果你老是这么感情用事  迟早会受不了
If you identify with too many clients, you burn out.
等我有什么事做对了你再提醒我  好吗
Why don't you tell me when I do something right, okay?
没问题
Sure.
陪审员那边就交给你了
You go and interview the jurors
而我则去查查监视镜头是怎么回事儿
And I'll try to figure out how a surveillance camera can lie.
没错  我曾是陪审团主席
That's right. I was the jury foreman.
希望你不介意回答我们几个问题  医生
And you don't mind answering a few questions for us, doctor?
以助于我们在重审中更好地扭转乾坤
It'll help us refine the case for the retrial.
没问题
No problem.
我不认为可以扭转乾坤
I don't think you'll need much refining.
此案事实清楚  证据确凿
Your case was very strong, very logical.
老实说  我觉得根本没必要对当事人进行重审
In fact, I'm not even sure why the other side went to trial.
我从头到尾都投得是赞成票
I voted for conviction right from the start.
好极了
Good.
你  你是指  无罪吗
You-you mean, acquittal.
不  是有罪
No, conviction.
但我是辩方律师
But I'm with the defense.
根本就没什么小卡车  她在说谎
She was lying about the pickup truck.
她手上还有枪弹残留
She had the gunshot residue on her hands.
能透露下由始至终都投有罪有多少人吗
Can I ask you how many voted for conviction from the start, sir?
-11票  -什么
- Eleven.- what?
但有一个始终坚持认为无罪
There was only one holdout.
就是九号陪审员
Juror number nine.
我们还跟她争论了三天
We argued with her for three days.
但法官说投票结果是
But the judge polled the jury
是六对六陷入了僵局啊
And they deadlocked six to six.
没错  法官只能宣布我们僵持不下
Yes, well, the judge would only declare us deadlocked
因为我们故意均衡了投票
If we were evenly split.
我们中的几个陪审员改变投票
So some of us agreed to change our vote
只是为了可以早日离开那儿
To not guilty just to get out of there.
如果不是九号陪审员
If it hadn't been for juror number nine
我们早就达成一致  判其有罪了
We would have convicted.
她说服不了我们又不肯妥协  大家都受不了了
She didn't convince us. she exhausted us.
不要帮我准备茶了  道瑞斯基夫人
No tea for me, Mrs. Duretsky.
不用客气
Suit yourself.
听其他陪审员说
So the other jurors
您就是那位一直固执己见的人  对吗
Said you were a holdout. Is that correct?
他们全都觉得自己精明完了
They all thought they were so much smarter than me.
同意我观点的票数却刚好跟他们一样
My vote counted just as much as theirs.
究竟是什么让你这么确信被告无罪呢
What exactly in the defense's case convinced you?
其实  老实说
Well, the whole thing, really.
我看人一向很准  只需一眼就能辩其好坏
I tend to look at a person and size them up pretty quickly.
那姑娘  我一眼就喜欢上她了
That lady, I liked her.
是说被告  詹妮弗吗
The defendant, Jennifer?
不  是辩方律师
No, that lawyer lady.
她从不对人摆架子
She never put on airs.
我就喜欢这样的人
I like that.
我只是想弄明白
Just so I'm clear.
辩护方提出詹妮弗手上的枪弹残留
The defense expert argued that the gunshot residue
是因为和第三人抗争所留
On Jennifer's hands came from the struggle.
-噢  我的小乖乖  -是你一直坚守无罪的原因吗
- Oh, so sweet. - Is that why you held out?
我根本就不知道你说得是啥
Oh, I don't know about that.
我不过是感情用事罢了
I just tend to get a feeling.
对吗  赛勒斯
Don't I, Cyrus?
杰姬
Hi, Jackie.
-怎么啦  -没什么
- What's wrong? - Nothing's wrong.
我刚刚看了下要洗的衣服
I was going through the laundry
发现有格雷斯的有些校服
And I think some of Grace's school clothes
不太合适
You would find inappropriate.
我们刚刚搬了家
We just moved away.
格雷斯离开了所有好友
Grace has left all her friends.
我希望你能多陪陪她
I need you to go easier on her.
我要说的是
All I said was
我可以带她去逛逛  帮她选条长裤
I could take her shopping and help her find pants
选条能衬得她更苗条又漂亮的
That would make her look slimmer.
她体重完全符合健康标准
She's at a perfectly healthy weight.
我可不希望她整天尽想着减肥美体
I don't want her to have body image issues.
她迟早都会想的
She'll only have body image issues
如果她的体重再一路飙升的话
If she keeps gaining weight.
艾丽西娅
Alicia.
等我回家了我们再继续这个话题  好吗
Um, we'll talk about this when I get home later, okay?
-好的  -再见
- All right. - Bye.
你知道新员工凯里这个人吗
You know the new associate Cary?
那个穿布里奥尼的家伙吗
The one in the brioni?
干嘛  我可是个非常善于观察的人呢
What? I'm observant.
没错  正是那个穿布里奥尼的家伙
Yes, the one in the brioni.
他对我说"胜利属于强者"
He said to me, "may the best man win."
那究竟是什么意思
What exactly does he mean by that?
我想他应该是指
What he means is something
我们没对你坦白
I thought we weren't making public.
坦白什么
What?
听着  我们只有一个副职的空缺
Look, we only have one associate position open.
所以我们打算同时聘用两个应聘者
So we agreed to hire two applicants,
然后在六个月之内决定谁去谁留
And in six months decide which one to retain.
如此说来  我得和凯里一争高下了
So this is a contest between me and Cary?
说得再难听点儿  这是场生死大战
It was either that or a cage match.
我只是希望你的法律援助案顺利
I'm just happy your pro bono's going well.
探视时间快结束了
Visiting hours are almost over.
听他们说有位探访者
They said a visitor.
我还以为是妈妈
I thought mom.
我一直很忙
I've been busy.
很高兴见到你
It's good to see you.
我需要你签几样东西
I need you to sign some things.
没问题
Okay.
房子里的东西我没能都拿走
We didn't get everything we wanted on the house.
市场不景气  不好卖
It's a bad market to sell.
我明白
I see that.
大部分费用都花在了你的诉讼费上
We used most of it for your court costs.
而我的薪水得用来支付房租
The rent will come out of my salary
孩子们也不得不去公立学校就读
And the kids are going to have to stay in public school.
他们怎么样了
How are they?
妈妈说她现在帮着打理家务
Mother says that she's helping out around the house.
他们都很好
They're good.
格雷斯总会因为衣服和你妈妈争论不休
Grace argues over clothes with your mother,
扎克也会利用你在学校交到朋友了
And Zach is using you to make friends at school.
我都不知道这该说是好事
Which I don't know if that's a healthy thing
还是坏事
Or something worse.
利用我
Using me?
Funnyordie网站上有关于你的片段
Funnyordie has a skit about you.
我想  对他而言这是件很酷的事儿
It's cool, I guess.
瞧瞧吧
Here.
艾丽西娅  我知道这让你倍受煎熬
Alicia, I know this has been hard on you,
但你得相信我
But you have to believe me.
我是清白的
I'm innocent...
关于挪用公款这事
Of the abuse of office charges.
你以为我会相信你的鬼话吗  彼得
You think I give a damn about that, Peter?
他们在格雷斯电脑室里放了一段
They were playing a tape in Grace's computer lab
你吮吸一个妓女脚趾头的录像
Of you sucking the toes of a hooker.
你以为我会在乎你们雇佣合同里
You think I care about the small print
那些附属细则吗
In your employment contract?
听我说  我是被陷害的  州检察官
Come on, I was set up. the state attorneys...
得了吧  彼得  我不想再费唇舌了
Oh, come on, Peter. I don't want to talk...!
我不会和你吵架
I'm not going to fight.
我来这里不是和你吵架的
I didn't come here to fight.
妈妈说你接手了一个案子
Mom says you're on a case.
恭喜
Congratulations.
是那个伪装劫车案吗
The fake carjacking, right?
法官是谁
Who's the judge?
理查德·奎斯特
Richard Cuesta.
你不是在开玩笑吧
You're kidding.
他和我有仇
He hates me.
我知道
I know.
探访时间到了
Visiting hours are now over.
你知道这个案子有
You know there was something weird
些许蹊跷  不是吗
about that case, don't you?
那个刘易斯案件
The Lewis case?
有流言称
There was a rumor going around
有些证据被掩盖了  埋没了
That something got buried, pitted.
什么东西
What?
证物
Evidence
或是证词
Or testimony.
我该走了
I should go.
听着
Hey, listen,
谢谢你这么久操劳家计
Thanks for playing the breadwinner for a while.
我不会让你永远这么辛劳的
It's not going to last forever.
我的律师认为受理上诉的法院
The lawyers think the appellate court
愿意听证我的案子
Is going to hear my case.
如果他们改判  所有事情都会回到原样
If they overturn it, everything goes back to normal.
是时候走了
It's time.
彼得
Peter,
永远不可能回到原样了
It's never going back to normal.
警方一发现詹妮弗手中枪弹残留
As soon as the cops found gunshot residue
就断定她是嫌疑人
On Jennifer's hands, they had their suspect.
那如果他们忽视了其他的细节呢
So what if they pitted everything else?
如果他们并没有忽视呢
And what if they didn't?
在这儿争论毫无意义
Arguments are cheap.
那是什么
What's that?
犯罪实验室分析结果综述第一页
Page one of the crime lab summary.
我仔细看了才发现证据  看左上角
I was digging through discovery. Look at the top corner.
看起来像个订书钉
Looks like a staple.
确实是订书钉
It is a staple.
这很奇怪因为
And that's odd because...?
没有第二页
There's no page two.
如果没有第二页
Why do they need a staple
他们为什么要用订书钉
If there's no page two?
你认为警方隐瞒了一些指向另外一个
You think the cops kept something out of the discovery
嫌疑人的证据
That pointed to another suspect?
我认为他们做了  要不就在法庭上
Well, I think either they did or it would be helpful
暗示他们做了
In court to imply that they did.
离开庭还有两天
Two days away from trial
你却想放弃原先的策略
And you're thinking of dropping the old strategy?
戴安仅仅说服了养猫老妇被告无罪
Diane barely convinced a cat lady to acquit.
一辆卡车被人看到疾驰
So, a pickup truck is seen racing
穿过灯光明亮  空荡荡的停车场
Through a well-lit, empty parking lot.
一辆卡车怎么可能从监控摄像头下溜走呢
How is a truck missed by that surveillance camera?
标记错误时间的监控录像
Mismarked surveillance tape.
有了
Yeah.
你在做什么
What are you doing?
工作
Working.
这可比传票强多了
These are better than subpoenas.
我们只需要弄清监控系统的运作方式
We just need to see how the surveillance system works,
我们五分钟就可以搞定走人了
And we'll be out of your hair in five minutes.
-五分钟  -是的
- Five minutes? - Uh-huh.
好的  这里往下走就到了
Okay, it's down here.
我丈夫为什么要炒你鱿鱼
Why did my husband fire you?
他指责我干了两份活
He accused me of working two jobs.
你有吗
Were you?
是的
Oh, yeah.
瞧  计算机自动录下了监控记录
See, the computer automatically records the surveillance.
并标注了日期时间
Marks it with date and time.
-那是谋杀当晚的录像吗  -是的
- Is that the night of the murder? - Yeah.
就算是计算机错误地标注了日期时间
I mean, even if the computer did mismark it,
我在停车场巡视了一小时
I make an hourly tour of the lot,
没有看到小卡车
And I didn't see no pickup truck.
瞧  那个人就是我
Look, that's me.
十一点零三分  就在谋杀案发生前
11:03, just before the murder.
我们可以拿一份拷贝吗
Can we get copies of these?
当然可以
Sure.
蕾妮
Lanie?
Lanie?!
什么事
What?
给我拿几个磁盘
Get me some disks.
好的
All right.
你的机器多吐出一罐可乐
Your machine spit out an extra one.
你要喝吗
Would you like it?
多漂亮的孩子啊
Oh, what beautiful children.
一对儿女  一对儿孙女
Two kids, two grandkids.
蕾妮  那些磁盘怎么样了
Hey, Lanie, how about those disks?!
他总是这么可爱吗
Is he always so charming?
他只是个懒散的商场保安
Oh, he's just a lazy mall cop.
他要花半天时间看黄色录像
He spends half the day surfing porn,
而到了值夜班的时候
And with night shift,
他就赖在椅子上了
He can't get his skinny ass out of his chair.
总是要我早上去叫醒他
I'm always waking him up in the morning.
男人啊
Oh! Men.
我和彼得谈过  他说你去看他了
I talked to Peter. He said you dropped by.
我去了
I did.
我很高兴
I'm glad.
他在那里倍受煎熬
He's hurting in there.
他很勇敢
He's very brave.
但他在受煎熬
But he's hurting.
他需要你的原谅  艾丽西娅
He needs you to forgive him, Alicia.
杰姬
Jackie,
我给他当了15年的洗衣娘
I spent 15 years doing his laundry,
打扫他的房间
Cleaning his house,
从来没有任何质疑
Never asking a single question
因为我觉得没什么好质疑的
Because I didn't think I had to.
他带走了我们的全部共同财产
And he took everything I thought we had
然后送给了每一个人
And he just put it out there for everyone.
他也不想的
He didn't want that.
那种压力...
The press...
杰姬
Oh, Jackie,
别说了  彼得根本没替我们着想
Stop it, please! Peter wasn't thinking of us.
这需要时间  艾丽西娅
It takes time, Alicia.
给他点时间
Give it time.
我现在的时间都放在这些锅碗瓢盆上了
Any time I have right now is for them.
我想让她死
I want her dead.
我也是  只是时候未到
Me, too, just not quite yet.
那为什么扎克和我不能自己照顾自己
So why can't Zach and I just watch ourselves?
亲爱的  她每天只在这里呆几个小时
Honey, she's only here a couple of hours a day.
杀伤力极强的几小时
A couple very damaging hours.
你能应付的
You'll heal.
把她的来电铃声换了
And change her ring tone.
请报出您的姓名
Please state your name.
辛迪·刘易斯
Cindy Lewis.
你嫁给被害人多久了
And you were married to the victim
刘易斯太太
For how long, Mrs. Lewis?
快2年了
Two years until...
-谢谢  -你认为
- Thank you. - And how would you describe
你丈夫和他前妻的关系如何
Your husband's relationship with his first wife?
通常情况下都不错  甚至很友好
Well, most of the time it was fine, friendly even,
但在最后一次听证会后
But after the last custody hearing,
迈克尔为詹妮弗而感到担忧
Michael was pretty worried about Jennifer...
反对 法官大人
Objection, your honor.
反对理由
On what grounds?
无事实依据
Hearsay.
理由不错  福瑞克律师  反对无效
Nice try, Mrs. Florrick. I'll allow it.
继续  刘易斯太太
Go ahead, Mrs. Lewis.
他担心詹妮弗意图要
Um, he was worried jennifer was intent
得到单方监护权
On getting sole custody.
谢谢  刘易斯太太
Thank you, Mrs. Lewis.
辩方律师
Your witness.
刘易斯太太  你说迈克尔担心詹尼弗
Now, Mrs. Lewis, you stated that Michael was worried
然而在接下来的一周
About Jennifer, yet in the week following...
反对 法官大人
Objection, your honor.
反对有效
Sustained.
刘易斯太太  你声称
In your testimony, Mrs. Lewis, you claimed
詹尼弗想得到单方监护权
That Jennifer wanted sole custody,
但是否...
But isn't it true...?
-反对  -反对有效
- Objection.  - Sustained.
继续试  福瑞克律师  你会问到重点的
Keep trying, Mrs. Florrick. you'll hit on it.
刘易斯太太
Mrs. Lewis,
是谁提出去吃晚饭的
Whose idea was it to have dinner,
詹妮弗还是迈克尔
Jennifer's or Michael's?
迈克尔
Michael's.
这难道不能表明
So wouldn't that suggest
他的态度已经有所转变了吗
That his attitude had changed towards...?
反对
Objection.
反对有效
Sustained.
谢谢
Thank you.
冷静点
Clam down
布里格斯警官  辩方提到案发当时
Now, detective Briggs, the defense has referred
在案发点附近有三起未破获的劫车案
To three unsolved carjackings in the neighborhood at that time.
-您知道此事吗  -知道
- Are you aware of this?  - I am.
那您怎么知道本案
So why didn't you consider this incident
不是又一起连环劫车案呢
To be another in that series of carjackings?
首先  被抢的都是豪华汽车
Firse of all are luxury cars
一辆雷克萨斯和两辆宝马
One LEXUS and two BMWs.
而本案被害人驾驶的是2001款的本田
The victim in this crime was driving a 2001 Honda,
并且燃油管上没发现剪切的痕迹
And there was no clip on the fuel line.
劫车者通常都会剪切燃油管
This is what the carjackers did
来使豪华车抛锚
To force the luxury cars over.
没错
That's right.
但本案受害人只是因为车胎漏气了
But in the case of the honda, the victim pulled over
才将本田停在了路边
Because he had a flat.
是的 女士 我们在车的前轮上
Yes, ma'am, there was a nail driven
发现一枚钉子
Into the front driver tire.
明白了  那为什么劫车者
I see. now, why is this something
就不会选用钉子呢  探长
A carjacker would never do, detective?
那只会适得其反
It would defeat the purpose.
车胎都漏气了  你还怎么偷车
I mean, how do you steal a car with a flat?
辩方律师
Your witness.
情况并不乐观  对吗
It's not going well, is it?
现在还言之尚早
It's early.
福瑞克律师
Mrs. Florrick?
布里格斯警官  "坑"是什么意思
Detective Briggs, what is "the pit"?
你说什么
Excuse me?
在警界  "坑"是指什么
In police circles, what is "the pit"?
反对  法官大人
Objection, your honor.
反对理由
On what grounds?
理由是...引导证人
On the grounds that... relevance.
那我们来看看能引导到什么程度好了
Well, let us see how relevant this becomes, Shall we?
警官
Detective?
"坑"是...
The pit...
是警局的暗语
The pit is police slang
是指被认为与犯罪现场无关的证据
For evidence thought irrelevant at a crime scene.
所以  如果说一名警官提到要将某样东西
So when an officer's referring to dropping something
丢到"坑"里  或是要让它变成"坑"
In "the pit," or "pitting it,"
他是指什么
he refers to what?
是指将这件东西从犯罪现场排除
Excluding it from the crime scene narrative.
但我们排除的都是不相关的资料
But that only applies to irrelevant details.
我们是不会排除与案件有关的证据的
We wouldn't exclude pertinent evidence.
在刘易斯案中有没有证据被排除
Was anything pitted from the Lewis crime...?
法官大人  反对
Your honor, objection!
证据一直都是登记在案的
Evidence is logged in all the time
这证明了新的发现与本案无关
That proves irrelevant to the discovery.
我这不是为了混淆视听
It's not an intent to deceive.
只是想尝试解读真相
It's an attempt to decipher facts.
我们并不知道这是否...
We don't even know if it is...
我还要指责辩方没有提供任何一条
And to blame the prosecution for not coming up with every
-有依据的信息  -她只是抓住案子
-Single possible detail?!  - She's trying to build
-的重点  -够了  福瑞克律师
- A case on a staple...  - okay, okay, Mrs. Florrick!
这些内容都没有在初审的时候提出
None of this was in the first trial.
你是想提出新的辩辞吗
Is it your intention to pursue a new defense?
是的  法官大人
Yes, your honor.
辩方律师是在试图引导陪审团
Counsel's trying to mislead the jury.
她是在暗示一桩警界腐败案
She's implying there was police corruption.
闭嘴  马坦
Oh, shut up, Matan!
她是否说对了  这才是问题所在
Is she right? That's the question.
你有没有隐瞒什么
Did you bury something?
我们都知道这是怎么回事
We all know what's going on here.
彼得·福瑞克是个腐败的
Peter Florrick was a corrupt
并且已经被定罪的州检察官
And convicted state's attorney.
即使有证据被隐瞒  也是他隐瞒的
If evidence was buried, he buried it.
现在她学到了她丈夫那手
And now she's benefiting from his knowledge.
你拿来的材料
Which still leaves you
也是少了几页的
With some pages missing here!
我要你周一之前
I'll give you till Monday
把他们补齐
To produce them
还要呈上他们提过的所有证据
Along with any evidence they reference.
那时我再进行裁决
Then I'll rule on admissibility.
至于你  福瑞克律师
And you, Mrs. florrick,
这些东西我不清楚是别人给你的
I'm not sure if you're being fed this stuff,
还是你自己找到的
Or you doing on your own,
但如果是前者
But if it's the former,
那你就是在铤而走险  挑战道德底线
You're walking a very narrow ethical line here.
你明白吗
You understand that?
明白  法官大人
Yes, your honor.
指令很简单
The directive was simple.
按照第一阶段审讯的套路就行了
Follow the strategy of the first trial.
不过  你得拼命去搜集那些
Instead, you're pushing for evidence
即使对你的案子毫无帮助的证据
That might not even help your case.
我和第一陪审团会谈过
I interviewed the first jury,
他们以11:1的投票予以定罪
And they voted 11 to one to convict.
对不起  不是这样的  当时双方票数相等
Excuse me. That's not true. It was evenly split.
不  有一半的陪审员改变了投票
No. Half the jurors switched their votes
虽然没有全数通过就不能开庭
When they couldn't get a troubled juror to deliberate.
所以我运用了自己的判断力来改变策略
So, I used my judgement to change strategies.
你的判断力就是不及时向我们反馈信息吗
And was it your judgement not to update us?
她只是初级助理
She's a junior associate
却自视过高
Who doesn't think she's a junior associate.
他丈夫曾是州检察官
Her husband was a state's attorney.
她过去住在高地公园
She lived in highland park.
这不只是在训练一只老狗
It's not just teaching an old dog new tricks.
而是在训练一只骄傲的老狗
It's teaching an entitled dog new tricks.
好了  戴安  关键是她在搜集那些
Come on, Diane. The problem is she's catching evidence
被你忽视的证据
That you overlooked.
我知道你教导过不少女律师
I've seen you mentor these women
直到她们开始与你竞争
Until they start competing with you.
-然后你....  - 什么  你在说什么
- And then you...  - What? Excuse me?
我提议惩戒一下艾丽西娅
I say we reprimand Alicia
任命凯里为首席律师
And put Cary in as first chair.
谢谢
Thank you.
肯定是她  对吗
That's her, isn't it?
索尼娅  你能不能....
Sonia, can you...?
艾丽西娅·福瑞克的办公室
Alicia florrick's office.
请稍等
One moment, please.
詹尼弗  接电话
Jennifer, pick up.
喂
Hello?
你好  宝贝儿
Hi, baby.
我好想你
I miss you so much.
艾丽西娅
Alicia.
是狗毛
It's dog hair.
被掩埋了的证据
The pitted evidence.
我和一个取证室的一个朋友谈过
I talked to a friend at the crime lab.
他让我查阅了证据记录
Gave me a preview of the evidence.
记录
A preview?
受害者的身上发现有狗毛
It's dog hair found on the victim's clothes.
警察排除了这点
Cops pitted it
因为他们在迈克尔的住处也发现了狗毛
Because they found dog hair at Michael's residence
他们猜测属于同一只狗
And thought it was the same.
结果不是吗
But it's not?
那是只意大利灵提
It's from an Italian greyhound.
迈克尔和詹尼弗都没养过这种狗
Neither Michael nor Jennifer had greyhounds.
还有  狗毛上有一种药剂成分
So also, a chemica on the hair...
爱克托林
Alco ectolin...
一种用于肌肉和关节疼痛的犬用药剂
A lotion for muscle and joint pain.
那是化学元素号码吗
That's the chemical number?
不  是他的手机号
No, his cell number.
我答应陪他喝一杯
I agreed to drinks.
所以我们现在要找的是
So we're looking
一只患有关节病的意大利灵提的饲养者
For an arthritic greyhound owner.
我们  我听说你被降为列座律师了
We? I hear you're being bumped to second chair.
什么时候
When?
明天下班
End of tomorrow.
凯里被提升了
Cary's being transitioned in.
他会采用第一阶段审讯的策略
And he'll go back to the first trial strategy.
他这一年坏运不断
It's not a good year for him.
现在  这位全明星后卫又要
The all-star point guard is currently suing
控告他的前女友伤害罪
His ex-girlfriend for damages,
希望法官最终能裁定
Hoping the judge can finally determine
这个案子是实情还是炒作
Whether this case was fact or fantasy.
你可能只知道她叫  "安贝儿"
You know her simply as "Amber,"
是个曾使州检察官--芝加哥坏小子
The young woman who brought down
彼得·福瑞克堕落的年轻女人
Bad boy Chicago state's attorney Peter Florrick.
尽管她表示想把这件丑闻抛到脑后
Though she says she wants to leave the scandal far behind,
但这位应召女郎安贝儿·麦迪逊
Celebrity call girl Amber Madison
其实已决定要写一本她和福瑞克的回忆录
Has decided to write a memoir about her time with florrick.
在内部的独家报道中...
In this exclusive interview with Inside Edition...
你真的还要工作啊
Do you really have to work?
对  还需要十多分钟
Yeah, ten more minutes.
扎克  我用下你的电脑
Zack, I need your computer.
妈妈  我刚升级了我的警告级别
Mom, I just raised my wanted level.
好的  宝贝儿  我替你高兴
Yeah, I'm happy for you, honey.
当彼得的父亲在伊利诺斯州法院工作时
When Peter's father was on the illinois court,
他从来不把案子带回家  一次也没有
He never brought a single case home, not once.
他是法官  杰姬  我只是初级助理  扎克
He was a judge, Jackie. I'm a junior associate. Zach?!
帮我把这两个盘放在一起进行对比播放
I need you to play These two computer disks side by side.
能把我的电脑和你的放一块吗
Can you set up my computer next to yours?
你妹妹怎么样了
Hey, how's your sister?
她还在和奶奶对抗吗
She still fighting with grandma?
这是什么
What is it?
这是凶案当晚的一个视频
It's video Of the night of the murder.
就是一些死者的遗容
Like faces of death?
妈妈  我看过更可怕的
Mom, I've seen worse.
你真可爱
You're adorable.
哪有
I'm not.
是的  你很可爱
Yes, you are.
扎克  定住画面
Zach, freeze it!
怎么了  那是什么
What? What is it?
是证据
It's proof.
诺斯先生  这是谋杀当晚11点03分
This is at 11:03 the night of the murder, Mr. North,
那是你
And... that's you
在停车场每小时巡逻一次  对吗
Making your hourly circuit of the lot, correct?
是的
Yes, that's correct.
你没有看到小货车或劫车人跑过
And you saw no pickup truck, no carjacker racing past,
没看到任何被告宣称她看到的东西
Nothing the defendant Claims she saw.
是的
That's correct.
谢谢
Thank you.
没有问题了  法官大人
Nothing further, your honor.
福瑞克律师
Mrs. Florrick.
请将监控录像拿进来好吗
Can we have the monitors in, please?
谢谢
Thank you.
州检察官来了
State's attorney's here.
诺斯先生
Now, Mr. North...
他们现在担心她会
They're worried she's getting
从她丈夫那学到些技巧
The stuff from her husband.
这是三个图像
Here are three images.
中间是15号晚的监控录像
The middle is the image of the surveillance from the 15th,
也就是案发当晚
The night of the murder,
左边是14号晚的录像
And the one over there on the left is the image from the 14th,
也就是案发的前一晚
The night before the murder, and the one
右边是16号的  也就是案发后的第二晚
On the right is from the 16th, the night after the murder.
你能看到上面的日期吗
Can you see the dates on those?
是的  可以
Uh, yes, I can.
按照你之前说的  那个人是你
So, as you said before, there you are
当时是案发当晚的11点03分
The night of the murder, at 11:03,
你在停车场巡逻
Making your circuit of the lot.
这个则是你在案发前一晚
And... there you are the night before the murder
再看案发后第二晚  你也在做相同的事
And the night after, doing the same thing.
-这肯定很闷  -不会  女士
- It must get old. - Um, no, Madam.
我的工作没有你的报酬多  但我爱它
My job doesn't pay as much as yours, but i still love it.
很好
Okay, good.
现在  诺斯先生
Now, Mr. North,
我们快进一下  可以吗
Let's fast-forward, shall we?
案发当晚  45分钟后
45 minutes...the night of the murder.
那个
And there.
你看到什么了
What do you see?
-没什么  -没有吗
- Nothing. - No?
就在那里  也许你
It's right there...maybe you
需要靠近点
Need to move in a little closer.
是个购物袋  看上去像个购物袋
Oh, it's a shopping bag, it looks like a shopping bag.
事实上  那就是购物袋
Actually, it is.
是个塑料购物袋
It's a plastic shopping bag.
当晚风很大  那塑料袋被吹过停车场
It was a very windy night that night, and it blew across the lot
-在11点48分  -法官大人  反对
- At 11:48. - Your honor, objection.
-这与本案有什么关系  -我也不知道
- What does it have to do with anything. - Beats me.
但我很感兴趣  你呢  布罗迪先生
But I'm interested, aren't you, Mr. Brody?
反对无效
Overruled.
好的  那么我们将其他两个录像
Okay, so let's fast-forward the other two monitors
案发前和案发后的录像
The night before the murder and the night after the murder
快进到同一个时间点
To the same time code.
这是14号的
Here's the 14th...
这是16号的
And the 16th.
你看到什么了
What do you see?
我不知道
Um... I don't know.
我认为你知道  先生
I think you do know, sir.
要么是你让一个塑料袋
Either you have a plastic bag
每晚11点48分被吹过停车场
Blow across your lot every night at 11:48,
要么这些就是同一卷录像的复本
Or these are duplicates of the same tape.
不是的
No, it...
不是你们看到的那样
It's not wh-what it looks like.
我明白  先生
I understand, Sir.
你并不是有意要误导警察
You didn't willfully mislead the police.
是的  没错
Yeah, that's correct.
只是天越来越冷  所以有时候
No, it's just that it gets cold out there, and sometimes
-你没去停车场巡逻  -是的
- You don't make the circuit of the lot. - Yes.
所以当你不去巡逻时
So on the nights that you don't go out,
你就不录下当晚的监控图像
You don't record the actual surveillance image,
你将电脑设置好
You set your computer up
复制前一天晚上的图像
To duplicate the night before,
以防经理检查
Just in case your manager checks in,
是这样吗
Is that correct?
是的
Yes.
因此我确定
Just so I'm clear,
案发当晚没有录像
There is no recording the night of the murder,
而且你也没在那看到或没看到
And you were never there to see or not see
小货车或劫车者
The pickup truck or the carjacker.
对不起
I'm sorry.
是的
Uh, yes.
没有问题了
No further questions.
所以你在想
So, you're wondering whether demolishing
推翻控方主要证人
The key prosecution witness
是否能保住你首席的位置
Didn't just save your ass as first chair
干得好  顺便说一句
Nice work, by the way.
谢谢
Thanks.
但那的确足以进行合理的怀疑
But was that enough for reasonable doubt.
知道是什么害了你吗
You know what hurts you?
-轮胎里的钉子  -是的
- Nail in the tire. - Yep.
还有那过时的本田
And the old Honda.
这感觉不像是劫车案
It just doesn't feel like a carjacking.
像是谋杀伪造得像劫车案
It feels like a murder Made to look like a carjacking.
如果我不进行辩护会怎样
What if I don't fight it?
什么  承认这就是个谋杀吗
What, agree that it was just a murder?
那么陪审团就会要你指出一个嫌犯
Then the jury needs a suspect.
太晚了
It's late.
就像以前
It's like old times.
举证程序
Evidentiary procedure.
模拟审判
The mock trial.
你记得这个啊
You remember that?
我怎么会忘呢
How could I forget?
-那个案子我们输了吗  -是的
- Did we lose That one?  - Yeah!
福瑞克夫人  我只是想恭喜你
Um, Mrs. Florrick, I just want to say congratulations.
听说你在法庭上表现很好
I heard you did well in court.
谢谢  索尼娅
Thanks, Sonia.
索尼娅
Sonia.
要走了吗
Heading out?
是啊  我和委托人约了一起吃早餐
Yeah. I got a breakfast meeting with clients.
怎么了
What?
有点儿不对劲
Something just doesn't seem right.
-迈克尔跟前妻吃饭  -对
- Michael has dinner with his first wife.  - Right.
他对詹尼弗说非常想她
He tells Jennifer he missed her,
-怀念他们共度的时光  -是啊
- Missed her all life together.  - Right.
-辛迪会怎么想  -第二个老婆吗
- What does Cindy think about it?  - The second wife?
辛迪会想不开
Cindy thinks some unhappy thoughts.
陪审团会同情她
Jury liked her.
那就想办法让他们不同情
Get them not to.
辛迪的哥哥呢  你查出什么情况
What did you get on Cindy's brother?
这些是他的就业记录
These are his employment records.
很好  尸检报告呢
Good. What about the lab report?
这儿  不过他们会一直提出反对的
Here. But they're gonna object the whole way.
你得自己顺藤摸瓜
You'll need to just string together
-作出整理  -福瑞克律师
- Some implications.  - Mrs. Florrick
有空吗
You have a moment?
我们从前应该没见过
I don't think we've ever met before.
我是格伦·查尔兹
I'm Glenn Childs.
我们见过了
We've met.
你知道他在利用你  对吧
You know he's using you, don't you?
彼得以为是我把他搞下台的
Peter blames me for his downfall.
所以利用你来对付我
He's using you to get to me.
你怎么想到的
How do you figure?
福瑞克女士
Mrs. Florrick, please.
是他让你追查被掩埋的证据的
He told you about the pitted trace evidence.
别给自己惹祸上身
Don't make yourself collateral damage here,
这是为你自己好
For your own sake.
查尔兹先生
Mr. Childs,
那天你把性丑闻录像带交给了媒体
The day you leaked that sex tape to the press
让我不得不挡着孩子们
And forced me to shield my children
不让他们看到所有电视台节目里
From every cable news station that played it
每天24小时的滚动播出
In a 24-hour rotation,
从那时起  我已经有祸在身了
That was the day I became collateral damage.
如果你担心的是我丈夫  查尔兹先生
If you're worried about my husband, Mr. Childs,
那您以前明显没有真正激怒过女人
You've obviously never made a woman angry before.
出庭好运
Well, good luck in court.
刘易斯女士  你和死者
Mrs. Lewis, did you and the deceased
签过婚前协议吗
Sign a prenuptial agreement?
是的  税务原因
Uh, yes, for tax purposes.
所以我们假设死者要和你离婚
So if the deceased were to divorce you, let's say,
是为了和前妻重修旧好
In order to reunite with his first wife..
反对
Objection.
反对有效
Sustained.
如果死者要和你离婚
If the deceased were to divorce you,
你将无权获得死者的婚前财产
You would be cut off from his premarital savings,
-是这样吗  -反对
- Is that correct?  - Objection.
-与本案无关  -反对有效
- Relevance.  - Sustained.
请更换问题  福瑞克女士
Move it along, Mrs. Florrick.
刘易斯女士  您在证词中说
Mrs. Lewis, you stated in your testimony
案发当时
That you were in Miami
您在迈阿密
At the time of the shooting visiting family,
所以警方从未怀疑或询问过您
So the police never suspected or questioned you of the murder?
怀疑我是凶手吗  对  当然没有
Of the murder? No, of course not.
那您哥哥呢
What about your brother?
反对  法官大人  拜托
Objection! Your honor, come on,
辩方律师的整个讯问过程就是个烟雾弹
This whole line of questioning is a smokescreen.
布罗迪先生  我们还是先等等
Mr. Brody, why don't we wait
等真的有烟雾出来  再说这是烟雾弹吧
For a whiff of smoke before we call it a screen, please.
反对无效
I'll allow.
警方从未询问过您哥哥
The police never questioned your brother,
是吗  刘易斯女士
Isn't that correct, Mrs. Lewis?
他们没理由这么做
Well, they had no reason to.
因为他住在迈阿密吗
Because he lived in Miami?
因为丹尼与本案无关
Because Danny had nothing to do with this.
刘易斯女士  庭上已经接受了
Mrs. Lewis, the judge has admitted into evidence the buried...
留着吧
Strike that.
之前公布的证据作为本案的证据
...the previously unreleased trace evidence.
同时也接受了
He has also admitted into evidence
尸检出的一些意大利灵提的毛发
The crime lab's finding that these greyhound hairs were covered
上面有一种叫爱克托林的药物的残留物
In a chemical compound called Alco Ectolin.
您听说过吗
Have you heard of this?
不好意思  是一种药吗  没听过
Sorry, the chemical? No.
我也没听过
No, neither had I.
是一种外涂药剂
It is a lotion.
是涂在赛狗身上用来缓解...
It is a lotion that is used at dog racing tracks to ease...
-反对  跟证据不符  -反对有效
- Objection. Not in evidence. - Sustained.
布罗迪先生  你最好还是起立吧
And you might want to stay standing, Mr. Brody.
我有预感我们快看到你说的烟雾弹了
I have a feeling we're nearing your smokescreen.
刘易斯女士
Mrs. Lewis,
凶案发生一年前
Isn't it a fact
您哥哥在赛狗场工作过
That a year ago at the time of the murder,
这是事实吗
Your brother worked at a dog track?
反对
Objection!
反对有效
Sustained.
没有问题了
No further questions.
你还没喝呀
You're not just making this up?
拜托  喝之前还有一堆祝酒词呢
Come on it's still a lots of call tradition
为了首战告捷  敬你一杯
Your first jury trial-- shot of tequila.
喝吧
Let's go.
好吧
Okay.
我也干了
Yeah, I just made that up.
声音真好听  不是吗
Sounded good, though,  didn't it?
你猜陪审团会坚持多久
How long do you think they'll stay out?
我很久以前就不猜这个了
Oh, I stopped guessing about juries a while ago.
他们让你老公等了多长时间
How long were they out with your husband?
6小时
Six hours.
我有点不明白
You know what I don't get?
你为什么还支持他
Why you stood by him.
换了是我  我会一刀捅进他心脏
I would've stuck a knife in his heart
我一直觉得我也该这样
I always thought I would, too.
以前我听到人们的丑闻  想到那些老婆们时
But when I heard about those other scandals, the other wives...
我还在想...
I thought...
你们怎么能让自己这样被人利用
How can you allow yourself to be used like that?
然后事情就发生在我自己身上了
And then it happened,
我只是...
And I was...
...没有准备好
...unprepared.
你好
Hello?
好的
Yes.
谢谢
Thanks.
陪审团到了吗
Jury's in?
福瑞克律师
Well, Mrs. Florrick,
芝加哥杀人案已经决定
Chicago homicide has decided
重亲打开迈克尔·刘易斯遇害一案的
To reopen its investigation into
调查记录
The murder of Michael Lewis
布里格斯警官
Detective Briggs,
做了一项令人钦佩的尽职调查
Doing an admirable amount of due diligence,
已经确认辛迪·刘易斯的哥哥丹尼
Has confirmed that Cindy Lewis's brother Danny
在案发的同一周
Had access to his employer's pickup truck
钻进了他老板的小货车
The week of the murder.
而那些已被采纳为证物的狗毛
And the dog hairs Admitted into evidence
与在他工作地点找到的相吻合
Match those found at his workplace.
所以我们的州检察官
So our State's attorney,
凭借着他光芒四射的智慧
In his radiant wisdom,
已经决定撤销对你客户的控告了
Has decided to withdraw the charges against your client
并且立案侦查刘易斯先生弟弟的案件了
And pursue a case against Mrs. Lewis's brother.
这样没错吧  布罗迪先生
Isn't that right, Mr. Brody?
我只要听"是"或者"不是"
All I need is a yes or no.
是
Yes.
很好
Good.
那我们可以结案了
Then we're done here.
谢谢你  非常感谢
Thank you. Thank you so much.
杰姬
Hi, Jackie.
没事  只是晚了一点  没事的
No, it just went a little late, that's all.
我做了烤肉  我在想
I made a pot roast, and I was wondering
你回不回来吃晚饭
If you were coming home for dinner.
怎么了  我说啥了
What? What did I say?
没事  只是我过去也常常对彼得这么说
Nothing. It's just that's what I always used to say to Peter.
你还在吗
Are you there?
在  我只是还得去拿点东西
Yeah, yeah. I just need to pick up a few things,
很快就回来了
And I'll be home soon.
杰姬  我不知道我以前是否说过
Jackie, I don't know if I've said this,
但是  谢谢你  肯做出改进
But thank you... for stepping up.
我当然会这么做  为啥不会
Of course I would. Why wouldn't I?
待会儿见
I'll see you soon.
好的
All right, then.
再见
Good-bye.
抱歉
Oh. Hey. Sorry.
我不知道你在
I didn't know you were here.
这是点小小的心意
Just a little office token.
你做得很棒
You did great.
谢谢夸奖
Thanks.
我做得确实不错  是吧
I did, didn't I?
还有件事
Oh, one more thing.
什么事
Yes, sir?
你已经是我的民事诉讼案件的
You've been made my second chair
列座律师了
In the civil case.
明早九点半  员工会议上见
See you tomorrow at 9:30, staff meeting.
我会准时出席的
I'll be there.
是我
Hey, it's me.
很抱歉  你肯定已经睡了
I'm sorry, you must be in bed,
我只是想说
But I just want
高等法院同意重审我的案子了
The appellate court agreed to hear my case.
我到现在都不敢相信
I still can't believe it.
律师认为我们翻案有很大胜算
The lawyers think we have a really good shot at overturning this,
他们明天会做一个正式的声明
And they're gonna make an official statement tomorrow.
但是  我只是想先告诉你
But, uh, I just wanted to tell you first.
我会很快见到你的
I'll see you soon.